Seeno!
yes!
Wow!
This is amazing!
I'm sure there are no words for this
Yes, welcome
Welcome
Oh no!
Great, good luck!
This is amazing!
Boil everything and bake it
I'll be waiting in the morning
Sorry, wait!
Hello everyone!
Morning time has sounded! We
Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku
Abbreviated as Ebichu
Attendance number 15, Nonoka Kazami
Attendance number 17, Yuna Nakamura.
Yes, that's how it started!
Mugen company star pla collaboration!
Yay!
This program is a program in which the members of Mugen Company Starpla collaborate with companies and shops all over Japan to make you have fun and become energized.
What kind of collaboration is today?
Today, it's already behind here.
We will collaborate with Steak House Chicago.
Today, I think I'll try the one-day capacity experience.
I've never had a part-time job before, so it's my first time working at a store, so there are a lot of things I'm not used to, but I hope I can enjoy it.
Maybe I will be able to eat steak.
You just have to try your best
I hope I can do my best and eat a delicious steak.
So let's go right away
Let's go
Hello
Attendance number 15, Nonoka Kazami and
Attendance number 17 is Yuna Nakamura.
Thank you for your cooperation today.
thank you
Itabashi's chime rang.
We are Steak House Chicago.
thank you
Itabashi's chime rang
Thank you for coming to special events often.
Originally we are Ebichu family.
This struggle is so rewarding, thank you for letting me do it.
We met at Ebichu's live show and became friends from there.
I originally lived in Osaka.
I moved to Kanto so I could go to Ebichu's live shows as much as possible.
At that timing, I decided to work here.
Because you told me
It's really Ebichu-san
It's like a connection that connected me.
That's how I got to work this time.
Because I am connected
I was really looking forward to it
Wow really
happy
I asked you to say that.
You could say that connections lead to connections.
I'd like to do it in a way that really makes us feel really happy.
thank you.
Well, first I'm going to teach you how to grill and cut a delicious steak, so please move to the kitchen.
please.
Introducing the meat in the kitchen
Well, first of all, let me introduce the meat that we purchase at our store. This is the meat that comes in two pieces in this vat.
Our restaurant uses rib roast meat.
Rib roast?
Maybe you haven't eaten much.
It means ribs.
Rib roast means ribs.
The delicate flavor of the red meat and the rich flavor of the fatty meat are perfectly balanced.
Hey
Our restaurant uses this meat.
Wow!
looks delicious!
fun!
I see
Oh! It’s big!
It's huge
This is the meat
yes
I said the part near the bone earlier.
There are definitely some bumps here
First, check the bones
If there is bone left, there will inevitably be unevenness here, so check the bone first.If there is bone left, it will inevitably look like this.
Your mouth may get hurt when you eat it.
Except this first
This is covered by the employees.
Can you eat this kind of beef?
The food is too luxurious
Are you eating this nice beef? It's too luxurious to eat.
That's amazing
If it's an image, I'll cut it all out and save it.
I have an image of
How is Chicago doing?
The freshness is maintained from the cross section cut to order.
To be able to provide stable and delicious steaks
It's cut to fit the customer's needs.The attention to detail is amazing.Thank you very much.
I'll cut it for you.I'll give it to you at 10%.Yes.
From the early cut cross section, there are some unevenness in fat and 8-lined parts, so I have to adjust the shape.
Then I asked you to cut this part.
I'd like to adjust the 200g, so I'd like you to cut it by the number of grams.
But yes, Mr. Kazami gave 1.5 pounds.It's number 15, but it's 1.5.
Point: Mr. Nakamura has 1.7 because of 17 and
How many in terms of grams? 680 grams 680 grams?
I've never heard of it at a steak restaurant.
Ms. Nakamura's weighs 770 grams.
By the way, do you even make steaks of this size at this restaurant?
I've never made one before
Honestly, it's not standard even for our store.
I see
Then, would you mind if I let you see Kazami?
please.
1.5lb, 680g, right?
Huh!?
Assuming it's 200g?
This 200g is a hint that it is about this thick.
It's 680g, so I'll go with this amount.
I'll go.
Phew! Ah, but it might turn out unexpectedly.
Okay? I'll cut it all off.
Futto! Good!
Now it's cut!
I can ride it!
Excuse me. Boom! It's gone! I'll take it! I feel like I'm running out of time too.
Excuse me!
Don!
picture!
Well, another 900g
difficult!
This is amazing 200g
But it was quite helpful
This means it weighs 900g.
Okay, okay, okay
Next is Hina, which weighs 770g.
Please wait a moment. 770g. 770g. 770g. Okay, let's go.
it's okay. sorry. I think it's okay. But it might take a lot of power. It's difficult to cut because it's so thick.
It's tough. Okay.
I'm going to cut it, so please weigh it. I'm going to go now, so I'm going to go. 70 Ah, hahahaha, it's -180, so that means it's me. It's 1.5 pounds. This is the middle one.
It's perfectly fine to cut it right in the middle as you imagine it to be, but don't cut all the way to the bottom.
Yes, I can't cut it.
Good, good, good, good, let's open it once. yes. yes. Well then, how about a little more?
It feels good, it feels good.
The back of this is definitely connected, so the oil is connected.
Yes, the last one.
For the final finishing touch, if you cut it like this,
Wow, oh, that's amazing.
Yes, because it is shaped like a book of meat is born.
The meat book is too powerful.
yes.
Even if it's like this, it's still a little streaky, and the inside streaks are still visible.
There will be some hard parts
I wonder if there will still be some uneven baking.
That's what I think
here's the secret weapon
Oh!
secret weapon
What's this big?
Looks heavy
What do you think it will be used for?
Eh, this?
Isn't that what it is?
It's okay if you touch me
Umm
Isn't it a machine that shatters paper? A shredder? A shredder Isn't it a shredder? It's okay if you touch it.
shredder?
Isn't it a shredder?
This is called meat tender,
To make it easier to cook open or large pieces of meat,
It is a machine that cuts off the streaky parts inside, so
yes.
Secret weapon. Give me a little secret weapon.
Good, yes, yay
Oh, it's done. But that's fine. What do you think? I can do it now. early. good.
What do you think?
I'm very good at it.
I think it's a success because the sinew inside is cut properly.
thank you.
Next, I will season the meat.
So that you can enjoy the natural flavor of meat,
Seasoned with pepper.
Seasoned with pepper only. Seasoned with pepper only. It really tastes like the meat itself.
yes
Pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-papa
Shaped to be shaken
This means to pepper
guess
If you shake it, it will always be the same
Because it becomes sparse
It's going to be a little hard
In the form of applying it to this part
Seasoned with pepper
Hey
I'm coming
yes
But I don't get it at all
It's not even at all
What do you think?
yes
How many hours does it take to provide this?
use it so slowly
What do you think?
I think this is okay.
What an amazing time.
It's an interesting move.
Do you have an image of yourself cooking?
But I've never shaken this.
Have you never shaken it?
keep it up.
Ah, amazing.
Oh, I'm shaking it.
Tonton. Yes, that's right, I'm shaking it.
Yes, that's right, rhythmically
Tonton
yes
Ah, but something
It doesn't come out as I expected.
No, but
Good, good
But I still shake it
It's difficult
My steak is definitely spicy
Okay
yes
Yes, thank you
Wait, You probably overdoing it.
once
yes
Then let me do it
Please fix it up a bit
yes
I think this is okay
thank you
Well then from here on
I'm grilling meat.
A great time battle
It's a race against time.
yes
On this stove now
I have prepared two iron plates for you.
Light the fire and heat the iron plate for 2 minutes.
Seino, ignite!
Is this enough?
If you put it on right away, it's a race against time.
yes
I will explain what to do in 2 minutes.
I used a spatula to add as much oil as possible.
Raise the temperature of the meat while cooking the meat.
It's ready.Okay, can I have the meat?It's cooked in about 30 seconds.
The timer is set to go up, so when this timer reaches 30 seconds, please paste the meat on it.
I'm nervous, please.
yes
This is below
yes bottom
it's okay
amazing
under
yes
very difficult
It was really slanted.
Various things all at once
If you like, please sprinkle this all over the meat.
all over the meat
Well then
yes
thank you
looks delicious
before turning the meat
I'll add some garlic like this.
yes
Can I turn it over?
Are you going to type this?
Wow scary
I'm coming, Seino.
yes
looks delicious
Seeno!
Wow!
After that, it was time to start arranging the food.
Arrangement? Fast!
yes!
Formation is coming.
yes.
Boom!
Wow!
It's gonna burn! It's gonna burn!
Good luck! It's heavy! Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa -Yes, I'm going. keep it up.
keep it up.
I'm the best.
Okay, okay.
Ugh.
yes.
It's a little big, but it's okay.
OK. The wine is soaked in the heat of the griddle between these times, giving the meat its aroma.
amazing!
Scary! I can’t do it!
This completes the process.
Yay!
Looks really delicious
I would like to have it
soft
amazing
First of all, I will eat it as is.
Looks hot
This is dangerous
It's so soft that the more you chew, the more the juices become like a rag.
like a rag
I'll enjoy having this
It's big
It cost me one piece.
You were chewing all the time, weren't you?
-
amazing, they are so delicious that I have lost all vocabulary.
It's delicious
the chair moved back
I'm sure there are no words for this
Absolutely delicious combinations depend on absolutely delicious meat.
This is amazing. This is amazing. This is an absolutely delicious combination of absolutely delicious meat. Yes, this is amazing.
this is great
Yeah
I definitely recommend this
For this collaboration, I devised a sauce that matched the colors of the two members.
Can I eat it and guess what's inside?
got it
You made it for me.
Let's start with Mr. Hasami.
It's definitely a member color
It's turning white
I'll enjoy having this
Hmm!
delicious!
Huh?
Does it feel creamy?
creamy
delicious!
I think it has a rich flavor.
I wonder what this taste is?
It tastes like white sauce like gratin.
The correct answer is cream cheese sauce
Cream cheese?
I put a little bit of attention to the contents.
The richness of cream cheese and horseradish
Add a refreshing spiciness to this rich cheese.
This is a sauce that has been specially created so that you can eat it without getting tired of it.
Thank you very much for your attention to this matter.
thank you
Next, we will serve a sauce inspired by Yuna Nakamura's milk tea.
Yes, I'm sorry, please excuse me.
looks delicious
Wow, let's add a little bit of flavor.
I'll take it because I want to guess it.
Hmm
yes
Yeah yeah yeah
Yeah yeah yeah yeah
Doesn't it look like sesame?
I thought it looked like miso.
It's completely different.
I'm not saying it looks Japanese in any way, but it doesn't feel Japanese at all.
Kokubu felt that it was different from before.The correct answer is
To the high morning child
I have an original idea for Boober Creamy Garlic Sauce, but that's it.
I added the aroma of sesame seeds, and the shape is such that the aroma of sesame seeds remains no matter how you eat it, giving the image of a Western-style steak.
I hope you can enjoy the gap a little bit, so I asked you to pass the baton and enjoy the nice scent of sesame seeds.
The sound of the meat was so juicy that I could feel it and it was really delicious.I didn't listen to Sharik quite a lot, but thank you very much.The atmosphere and taste of both are completely different.
I thought this was big, but I feel like I can't go at all.
I thought it would be fun to have different flavors.
thank you
I'm starting to acquire some kitchen skills.
Actually, it's almost time for the store to open.
Until you actually cut the meat and make it.
Is it okay if I follow the steps?
Can you do it?
Let's do our best!
I will also support you
yes!
Is it true!
please!
Apply without pepper
I wonder what the first day of a part-time job is like?
Isn't it great to make something even on your first day at work?
It's about to open
I will do my best
One senior person
welcome
Hello, I'm fine. Hello, I'm fine.
Yes, please, I raised my hand.
Scarho Steak
What about insurance?
It's rare
You said rare.
That means 30 seconds.
Order will be placed
1Chicago Rare please
Since it's a 200g steak, can I ask Mr. Nakamura to come with it first?
yes
Is there anything I can do with the garnish during that time?
This is it
Please prepare one
1,2,3,4,5 pieces
yes
welcome
How many people?
2 people
There are two new people. Welcome, welcome, welcome. How many people? 2 people. 2 new people.
Yes, welcome.
welcome.
Hey hey hey.
Shall I cut another one?
Have it shaved off.
Sharpen.
Okay, then can I have you do this for me?
yes.
I don't have a place to stay.
Well then, next time.
What do you think?
It's not enough.
Not enough.
Is this around here? Around here.
It's not enough. Is that okay? It's not enough.
Yes yes
Tucker will appear
press
Order will be placed
One car boy medium rare
One lady medium rare
salad french
Oh, what?
engine engine
yes!
He said he was a one-car boy.
Cowboy is 400g
yes
Yes, it's OK
Can I put garlic on this?
Garlic is fine!
My hands...
It's not open, so you can just do it once.
Seino!
yes!
Thank you for giving me a ride...
Good! Good!
yes!
oh!
Then the butter...
Good! Good! Good!
yes!
Well, I'll do some wine.
Please! I'll have some wine, please.
it's crazy
keep it up
Please provide
chicago rare
yes
I have a relationship
You said you were a one-town boy.
I would like two companions please.
But it disappeared nicely
I'm sorry, I'd like 2 pieces for 2 new people, but it's cutting nicely. Good luck, good luck.
Two relatives
welcome
Do your best, do your best
It's OK It's OK
Is one 150g piece of meat okay?
150g
This is dangerous
Order will be placed
1 Sunago medium rare Sunago medium rare 1 Sambiak medium rare 1 Triso please!
Why aren't you doing this?
yes!
How many grams is next?
Then please wait a moment
yes!
3 people, 1 person
welcome!
Thank you! This... Cowboys and ladies, let's bake. Yes! 200 and... Yes, OK! 1 person, thank you for coming.
Let's grill Sirboy and Ladies
200 and then 300, right?
The doneness is medium-rare, so the whole thing is cooked in 1 minute.
Then I'll bake this when there's only one minute left.
Order will be placed
One Chicago Medium Rare
The ceiling please
yes!
I'm riding
Not a sticker
Ah! Vertical!
vertically
yes
Yes, thank you
Amazing video
Ah
Awesome
amazing
Sorry to have kept you waiting
To top it all off, the lady's steak is medium rare!
200g!
You're good at it!
Yes! Thank you!
Then, could you please make me another iron plate?
yes!
Customers are waiting!
Excuse me! Excuse me!
yes!
What to do after that?
garlic!
Garlic! Yes! 30 seconds left! 30 seconds left! Yes! Yes! What to do after that? Garlic! Garlic! Yes!
30 seconds left!
yes!
Spread it! Spread it!
10 seconds left! 10 seconds left!
10 seconds left!
ah!
Yes! Yes!
yes!
So, I can ride it!
Is this so?
Yes! It fits!
yes!
Sorry, I'll take it!
This is it!
Damn!
Kan-san, I'm watching you a lot! Sorry! I'm watching you a lot! I'm watching you a lot! Yes! Yes, I'm sorry, I'll take it. I'll take it.
Kano-san, I'm really looking at you.
Sorry!
I'm watching a lot, I'm watching a lot.
Oh no!
We offer 300g and Chicago steak.
Tattered.
thank you for your hard work.
Any kind of customer could come, but we asked them to play the role of a real customer.
Let me pull a prank on you
Our employees and staff
Wait, isn't that scarier?
That's always better
Wow, if you think that's not good.
thank you
Thank you for your hard work today.Thank you for your hard work.
Neither I nor Nonaka-chan have ever worked part-time.
Even when I go to say good morning, I just sit and wait.
No matter how late it is from now on
I'm trying not to think it's too late
It was really difficult though
I like steak more now
I feel like I want to improve even more.
It was a lot of work, but it was fun, and I was happy when everyone said it was delicious.
I felt like I understood the feelings of all the employees. I feel like I'm still waiting for them, but I feel like I've gotten too far ahead of myself.
I'm working so hard that I can't do anything, but I can't believe it's my first time.I'm working so hard that I can't believe it's my first time.
It was extremely fast and went smoothly.
I was grateful
thank you for your hard work
thank you
Actually, idols have more work experience than idols.
Because it's really rare
work at my own shop
Seeing you messing around
I didn't have a chance to see it very often
In that sense, it was a valuable experience that I rarely had the opportunity to experience.
In that sense, it was a valuable experience.
We have also done this.
As one Ebichu family
I collaborated with Ebichu and the members.
Inspired by our activities
I hope the place for Ebichu will expand more and more.
I think so.
Thank you for your continued support.Thank you for your continued support.
In commemoration of this collaboration
Named after our attendance number introduced in the video.
I'm number 15, so it's 1.5 pounds.
I'm number 17 so it's 1.7 pounds
yes huge steak
You can enjoy it at Chicago-san's store.
We have decided to sell special tickets.
Please enjoy the giant steak at Chicago.
There are other collaboration-only benefits so stay tuned!
What kind of benefits?
Please wait